Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Annotated, not numbered
      - P-S
        - Reddings - Class (is what you got), 1981; SR-27426; Reddings (Box 62)
          In same jacket as # SR-27425, SR-27427. 2 copies.
          Catalog # FZ 37175; A-side Matrix # AL 37175 1A
        - Reddings - Class (is what you got), 1981; SR-27427; Reddings (Box 62)
          In same jacket as # SR-27425, SR-27426. 2 copies.
        - Reddings - The awakening, 1980; SR-27428; Reddings (Box 62)
          Catalog # JZ 36875; A-side Matrix # AL 36875 AB
        - Reddings - Back to basics, 1983; SR-27429; Reddings (Box 62)
          In same jacket as # SR-27430. 2 copies.
          Catalog # FZ 38690; A-side Matrix # A9 G AL 38690-1C
        - Reddings - Back to basics, 1983; SR-27430; Reddings (Box 62)
          In same jacket as # SR-27429. 2 copies.
        - Reds - Fatal slide, 1982; SR-27431; Reds (Box 62)
          Catalog # SPL-1048; A-side Matrix # SPL 1048 A
          Stony Plain Records
          Edmonton, Alberta, Canada
        - Reece, Alex - Acid lab, 1996; SR-27432; Reece, Alex (Box 62)
          Catalog # 12 BRW 344; A-side Matrix # 12 BRW 344 A1 MIKE'S- THE EXCHANGE
        - Reed, Jerry - Texas bound and flyin', 1980; SR-27433; Reed, Jerry (Box 62)
          Catalog # AHL1-3771; A-side Matrix # AHL1-3771 A MASTERFONICS
        - Reed, Jerry - The best of Jerry Reed, 1972; SR-27434; Reed, Jerry (Box 62)
          Catalog # AHL-1-4729; A-side Matrix # BPR2-1229 AHL1-4729-A
        - Reed, Vivian - Vivian Reed, 1981; SR-27435; Reed, Vivian (Box 62)
          Catalog # 67.790; A-side Matrix # 67790 A
          Carrere
        - Reeves, Martha - Skating in the streets (dancing in the streets); Then you came, 1979; SR-27436; Reeves, Martha (Box 62)
          Catalog # D-142; A-side Matrix # D-142A-1D
        - Reflections - Love on delivery, 1975; SR-27437; Reflections (Box 62)
          Catalog # ST-11460; A-side Matrix # ST-1-11460-Z4 #2
        - Reid, Clarence - Football freaks, 1981; SR-27438; Reid, Clarence (Box 62)
          Catalog # DD 6002; A-side Matrix # DD-6002 A FW/NY "CHAR"
          Dash
          Hialeah, Florida
        - Reproductive - You got to move, 1996; SR-27439; Reproductive (Box 62)
          Catalog # REPR 01; A-side Matrix # REPR0 1-A *-JTS-
          High Street Records
        - Reservoir - Pink machine, 1997; SR-27440; Reservoir (Box 62)
          Catalog # ZER LP 2150; A-side Matrix # ZER LP 2150 L-48692
          Zero Hour
        - Rev Run - Distortion, 2005; SR-27441; Rev Run; Simmons, Joseph (Box 62)
          Catalog # DEFF 16448-1; A-side Matrix # DEFF-16448-1-A-1
          Russel Simmons Music Group
        - Revelacion - The house of the rising sun, 1977; SR-27442; Revelacion (Box 63)
          Catalog # 733 402; A-side Matrix # Crocos 733402 A2
          Crocos Records
        - Reverb, Kelly - That's what I'm used to hearin'; Come out steppin', 1997; SR-27443; Reverb, Kelly (Box 63)
          Catalog # LS 001; A-side Matrix # 9708X16-A A2SP6II
          Lone Star Records
          Dallas, Texas
        - Reverb, Kelly - Under my control, 2001; SR-27444; Reverb, Kelly (Box 63)
          In same jacket as # SR-27445. Different discs.
          Catalog # LS 007; A-side Matrix # LS07 0103X34-A A+R SP6II
        - Fugees - Ready or not, 2004; SR-27445; Fugees; Aphrodite (Box 63)
          In same jacket as # SR-27444. Different discs. Test pressing
          Catalog # FUG001; A-side Matrix # FATLARRY EURODISC FUF001A MPO
        - Revolting Cocks - Big sexy land, 1986; SR-27446; Revolting Cocks (Box 63)
          Catalog # WAX 017; A-side Matrix # HUB pa-3-86 WAX-017-A
          Wax Trax! Records
        - Reynolds, Margaret - Think about it baby, 1987; SR-27447; Reynolds, Margaret (Box 63)
          Catalog # MAL 7442; A-side Matrix # (PXTR) MAL-7442 A G2A G1 B1
        - Rhibosome - Rhibosome EP, 2002; SR-27448; Rhibosome (Box 63)
          Catalog # HF 21; A-side Matrix # MW10460A2
          Hydrofunk Records
          Australia
        - Rhythm Kings - One for the money, 1989; SR-27449; Rhythm Kings (Box 63)
          Catalog # HS 008-12; A-side Matrix # HOUSE 008 A1 FOON MASTERING
          House Records
          Belgium
        - Rhyze - Just how sweet is your love, 1980; SR-27450; Rhyze (Box 63)
          Catalog # SAM 703; A-side Matrix # SAM-703-1-RE1 JR
          Sam Records
          Long Island City, New York
        - Ray, Ricardo - Aguzate, 1970; SR-27451; Ray, Ricardo; Cruz, Bobby (Box 63)
          Catalog # SLPA-8800; A-side Matrix # SLPA-8800-A K
          Alegre Records
        - Richie, Lionel - Dancing on the ceiling, 1986; SR-27452; Richie, Lionel (Box 63)
          Catalog # ZL72412; A-side Matrix # DM B-5514 A-1/7-86 II
        - Rico - On s'la donne, 1995; SR-27453; Rico (Box 63)
          Catalog # 529253-1; A-side Matrix # MP0 529253A1 JR
        - Riff Raff - Vinyl futures, 1981; SR-27454; Riff Raff (Box 63)
          Catalog # SD 32-108; A-side Matrix # ST-C-814715-A 0-15M 1-1
        - Riley, Teddy - The Harlem sessions, 1996; SR-27455; Riley, Teddy; Al B.; B. Fats (Box 63)
          Catalog # OSF LP 4019; A-side Matrix # TEDDY RILEY THE HARLEM SESSIONS OSF-LP 4019-A
          Ol' Skool Flava
        - Riley, Teddy - Nickel bag of swings, 1994; SR-27456; Riley, Teddy (Box 63)
          Catalog # TUF EP 3006; A-side Matrix # TUF EP 3006 A
          Tuff City
        - Rinder & Lewis - Cataclysm, 1980; SR-27457; Rinder & Lewis (Box 63)
          Catalog # AVI 6087; A-side Matrix # AVI 080-6087 A MP dp/WOODVAND
        - Rinder & Lewis - Warriors, 1979; SR-27458; Rinder & Lewis (Box 63)
          Catalog # AVI-6073; A-side Matrix # 069-6073 A Sheffield a-b 144
        - Ring - Jump!, 1979; SR-27459; Ring (Box 63)
          Catalog # SPV 28; A-side Matrix # SPV 28A-2A
        - Ring - Savage lover, 1979; SR-27460; Ring (Box 63)
          Catalog # SPV 23; A-side Matrix # SPV 23A-1A
        - Ringo - Eyewitness, 1982; SR-27461; Ringo (Box 63)
          Catalog # M.C. 002; A-side Matrix # DSR 5298-BS-SPIDERMAN RINGO LP EYEWITNESS
          MIC Productions
          Jamaica
        - Rios Sisters - I don't want you back, 1991; SR-27462; Rios Sisters (Box 63)
          In same jacket as # SR-27463. 2 copies.
          Catalog # ONN008; A-side Matrix # S-25051 ONN-008A F/W
          Onna Roll
          Forest Hills, New York
        - Rios Sisters - I don't want you back, 1991; SR-27463; Rios Sisters (Box 63)
          In same jacket as # SR-27462. 2 copies.
        - Riperton, Minnie - Minnie, 1979; SR-27464; Riperton, Minnie (Box 63)
          In same jacket as # SR-27465. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SO-11936; A-side Matrix # ST-1-SO-11936 Z3 #4
        - Riperton, Minnie - Minnie, 1979; SR-27465; Riperton, Minnie (Box 63)
          In same jacket as # SR-27464. 2 copies.
        - Riperton, Minnie - Love lives forever, 1980; SR-27466; Riperton, Minnie (Box 63)
          Catalog # SOO-12097; A-side Matrix # SOO-1-12097 Z3
        - Rising Love - Treasure chest, 1979; SR-27467; Rising Love; Braxton, Karen (Box 63)
          Catalog # VD-5005; A-side Matrix # VD-5005-AS
          Venture Records
        - Rita Mitsouko - The no comprendo, 1986; SR-27468; Rita Mitsouko (Box 63)
          Catalog # 70465; A-side Matrix # M6 355617 2
        - Ritmo Es Ritmo - La montagna mas alta; At Sunday, 1988; SR-27469; Ritmo Es Ritmo; Ritmo 2 (Box 63)
          Catalog # RITMO 2; A-side Matrix # RITMO 2-A
          HX Records
        - Rivera, Scarlet - Scarlet fever, 1978; SR-27470; Rivera, Scarlet (Box 63)
          Catalog # BSK 3174; A-side Matrix # BSK-1-3174-LW2 MCR
        - RJD2 - Deadringer (disc one), 2002; SR-27471; RJD2 (Box 63)
          In same jacket as # SR-27472. Double album.
          Catalog # DJX35; A-side Matrix # DJX35-1A
          Definitive Jux
        - RJD2 - Deadringer (disc two), 2002; SR-27472; RJD2 (Box 63)
          In same jacket as # SR-27471. Double album.
          Catalog # DJX35; A-side Matrix # DJX35-1C
        - R.J.'s Latest Arrival - R.J.'s Latest Arrival, 1985; SR-27473; R.J.'s Latest Arrival (Box 63)
          Catalog # 81260-1; A-side Matrix # ST A 855685-B 1-1
        - RMB - Break the silence; Everything, 1997; SR-27474; RMB (Box 63)
          In same jacket as # SR-27475. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 74321 49234 1; A-side Matrix # 743 214 923 41-A1
          Low Spirit Recordings
        - RMB - Break the silence; Everything, 1997; SR-27475; RMB (Box 63)
          In same jacket as # SR-27474. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 74321 49234 1; A-side Matrix # 744 214 923 41-A1
        - Robinson, Smokey - Being with you, 1981; SR-27476; Robinson, Smokey (Box 63)
          Catalog # T8-375M1; A-side Matrix # T8375-MIA 08B BAQ J-LEMAY
          Tamla
        - Robinson, Smokey - Blame it on love & all the great hits, 1983; SR-27477; Robinson, Smokey (Box 63)
          Catalog # 6064TL; A-side Matrix # EOD 6064 TLA 15-A zlz#12 C1
        - Robinson, Smokey - Smokin' (disc one), 1978; SR-27478; Robinson, Smokey (Box 63)
          In same jacket as # SR-27479. Double album.
          Catalog # T9-363A2; A-side Matrix # T9-363A2-A-18B
        - Robinson, Smokey - Smokin' (disc two), 1978; SR-27479; Robinson, Smokey (Box 63)
          In same jacket as # SR-27478. Double album.
          Catalog # T9-363A2; A-side Matrix # T9-363A2C-18B
        - Robinson, Smokey - Greatest hits vol. 2, 1967; SR-27480; Robinson, Smokey; Miracles (Box 63)
          Catalog # M5-210V1; A-side Matrix # M5-210V1-A-15C ZTL#13 BGM
        - Robinson, Smokey - Where there's smoke, 1979; SR-27481; Robinson, Smokey (Box 63)
          Catalog # T7-366 R1; A-side Matrix # T7-366R1-A-18A da
        - Robinson, Smokey - Touch the sky, 1983; SR-27482; Robinson, Smokey (Box 63)
          Catalog # 6030TL; A-side Matrix # 6030TL-A zny 15D#13 BMJ (T)
        - Rock & Roll Revival - The great oldies done hear & now - the Rock & Roll Revival, 1969; SR-27483; Rock & Roll Revival (Box 63)
          Catalog # DS-50059; A-side Matrix # DS-50059-A X13435
          ABC/Dunhill Records
        - Rock, Charlie - True love, 1996; SR-27484; Rock, Charlie (Box 63)
          Catalog # MRC 4512; A-side Matrix # MRC 4512-A DCHARLES
          Metropolitan Recording Corporation
          Newark, New Jersey
        - Rock III, Sir Monti - A piece of the rock, 1981; SR-27485; Rock III, Sir Monti; Rock, Monti (Box 63)
          Catalog # FS 366; A-side Matrix # FS 366A ALT 028-81 Ptz Hchfuch
          Everest Records Archive of Folk & Jazz Music
          Century City, California
        - Rock Ranger - Talk up, 1985; SR-27486; Rock Ranger; Invisibles; Sweet Talking J (Box 63)
          In same jacket as # SR-27487. 2 copies.
          Catalog # J.B. 5004; A-side Matrix # SC 778-AA GEE MR-GOODBAR''
          Joey Boy Records
        - Rock Ranger - Talk up, 1985; SR-27487; Rock Ranger; Invisibles; Sweet Talking J (Box 63)
          In same jacket as # SR-27486. 2 copies.
        - Rock Shock - Rock Shock, 1987; SR-27488; Rock Shock (Box 63)
          Catalog # RAZ 44001; A-side Matrix # RAZ 44001 A C1 G1 A-1
          Razmtaz
        - Rockers Revenge - Living for the weekend (let's work), 1984; SR-27489; Rockers Revenge; Calvin, Donnie; Johnson, Adrienne (Box 63)
          In same jacket as # SR-27490. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SWRL 2232; A-side Matrix # SWRL-2232-A-RE HERBIE JR
          Streetwise
        - Rockers Revenge - Living for the weekend (let's work), 1984; SR-27490; Rockers Revenge; Calvin, Donnie; Johnson, Adrienne (Box 63)
          In same jacket as # SR-27489. 2 copies.
        - Rockets - No ballads, 1980; SR-27491; Rockets (Box 63)
          Catalog # RS-1-3071; A-side Matrix # RS-1-3071-AS-RE1-CP2
          RSO
        - Rockets - Love transfusion, 1977; SR-27492; Rockets (Box 63)
          Catalog # BYL1-2572; A-side Matrix # BYL1-2572-A 5 -L NIX-ARDENT-
          Tortoise International
          Southfield, Michigan
        - Rockets - Live, 1980; SR-27493; Rockets (Box 63)
          Catalog # RKL 20197; A-side Matrix # 99RKL 20197-1L E1 11 2 90
          Rockland Records
        - Rocksann - She died, 1985; SR-27494; Rocksann (Box 63)
          Catalog # SC-666; A-side Matrix # WHO ELSE NICK ''BAY LOVE'', SONIA, JODI, DESI,AND CAROLE ANNE SC-666-A
          Street Corner
        - Rod - Shake it up, 1980; SR-27495; Rod (Box 63)
          Catalog # PRL 12180; A-side Matrix # P RL-12180 AS- 1E
        - Roger - Unlimited!, 1987; SR-27496; Roger (Box 63)
          Catalog # 1-25496; A-side Matrix # 1-25496-A- SR1 1-1 8587TD
          Reprise Records
        - Roger - The many facets of Roger, 1981; SR-27497; Roger (Box 63)
          Catalog # BSK 3594; A-side Matrix # BSK-1-3594-LW3
        - Rogers, D.J. - Love cycles, 1980; SR-27498; Rogers, D.J. (Box 64)
          Catalog # AS 771; A-side Matrix # XSS 167353-1C
        - Rogers, D.J. - Trust me, 1979; SR-27499; Rogers, D.J. (Box 64)
          In same jacket as # SR-27500. 2 copies.
          Catalog # JC 36002; A-side Matrix # PAL-36002-1D
        - Rogers, D.J. - Trust me, 1979; SR-27500; Rogers, D.J. (Box 64)
          In same jacket as # SR-27499. 2 copies.
        - Rogers, Lee - Sock some love power to me, 2000; SR-27501; Rogers, Lee (Box 64)
          Catalog # STS LP 6347; A-side Matrix # STS LP 6347-A SOCK SOME LOVE POWER TO ME
          Soul-Tay-Shus
        - Rogers, Timmie - Timmie Rogers as super soul brother alias "Clark Dark", 1974; SR-27502; Rogers, Timmie (Box 64)
          Catalog # PBS 2403; A-side Matrix # SON STXS-0715-4 PS-0559 -L NIX-
          Partee Records
          Memphis, Tennessee
        - Rokotto - Rokotto, 1978; SR-27503; Rokotto (Box 64)
          Catalog # ETAT 15; A-side Matrix # MELYS ETAT-15-A-1
          State Records
        - Rolling Stones - Their satanic majesties request, 1967; SR-27504; Rolling Stones (Box 64)
          Catalog # NPS-2; A-side Matrix # ZAL 8126-1D
          London Records
        - Rolling Stones - Start me up, 1981; SR-27505; Rolling Stones (Box 64)
          Catalog # PR 397; A-side Matrix # STPR-40243-1 1-1
          Rolling Stones Records
        - Rollins, Wayne - Street elements of flavor - ghetto style vol.1, 1996; SR-27506; Rollins, Wayne (Box 64)
          Catalog # CR-375; A-side Matrix # CR-375-A DMM SP1-1
        - Romanelli - Connecting flight, 1982; SR-27507; Romanelli; Romanelli, Roland (Box 64)
          Catalog # T1D 301; A-side Matrix # T1D-301-82-NP-5965-A PRC-C 1-1
          21 Records
        - Romanthony - Countdown 2000, 1999; SR-27508; Romanthony (Box 64)
          Catalog # GU48; A-side Matrix # 08 42379 20 1B1 GU 48
          Glasgow Underground
        - Romeo The One And Only - Romeo and Juliettski, 1988; SR-27509; Romeo The One And Only (Box 64)
          In same jacket as # SR-27510. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SR 12004; A-side Matrix # SR-12004-A
          Stolen Records
        - Romeo The One And Only - Romeo and Juliettski, 1988; SR-27510; Romeo The One And Only (Box 64)
          In same jacket as # SR-27509. 2 copies.
        - Romeo, Victor - Inside you (S Gurley remixes), 1998; SR-27511; Romeo, Victor (Box 64)
          Catalog # PPDT 32; A-side Matrix # PPDR 32-A FRESH --JTS--
          Public Demand
        - Romeo Void - Never say never, 1981; SR-27512; Romeo Void (Box 64)
          Catalog # 415A-0007; A-side Matrix # 415-A-0007-A
          415 Records
        - Roni Size Reprazent - Heroes, 1997; SR-27513; Roni Size Reprazent (Box 64)
          Catalog # 574 847-1; A-side Matrix # MPO TLX 25 A1
          Talkin' Loud
        - Roni Size Reprazent - New forms (disc one), 1997; SR-27514; Roni Size Reprazent (Box 64)
          Catalog # 536 498-1; A-side Matrix # MPO 536 498-1 A1
        - Roni Size Reprazent - New forms (disc two), 1997; SR-27515; Roni Size Reprazent (Box 64)
          Catalog # 537 498-1; A-side Matrix # MPO 536 499-1 A1
        - Roni Size Reprazent - New forms (disc three), 1997; SR-27516; Roni Size Reprazent (Box 64)
          Catalog # 538 498-1; A-side Matrix # MPO 536 500-1 A1
        - Roni Size Reprazent - New forms (disc four), 1997; SR-27517; Roni Size Reprazent (Box 64)
          Catalog # 539 498-1; A-side Matrix # MPO 536 501-1 A1
        - Roni Size Reprazent - New forms (disc five), 1997; SR-27518; Roni Size Reprazent (Box 64)
          Catalog # 540 498-1; A-side Matrix # MPO 536 502-1 A1
        - Roni Size Reprazent - New forms (disc one), 1997; SR-27519; Roni Size Reprazent (Box 64)
          Catalog # 534 934-1; A-side Matrix # MPO 534 934-1 A1
        - Roni Size Reprazent - New forms (disc four), 1997; SR-27520; Roni Size Reprazent (Box 64)
          Catalog # 534 937-1; A-side Matrix # MPO 534 937-1-AG2
        - Rootless - The mental spiritual EP, 1995; SR-27521; Rootless (Box 64)
          Catalog # WALLT 005; A-side Matrix # KEEP TAKING THE TABLA'S WALLT 005 A1 MIKE'S-THE EXCHANGE DAMONT
        - Roots - The tipping point (disc one), 2004; SR-27522; Roots (Box 64)
          In same jacket as # SR-27523. Double album.
          Catalog # B0002573-01; A-side Matrix # B0002573-01-A RJ
          Geffen Records
        - Roots - The tipping point (disc two), 2004; SR-27523; Roots (Box 64)
          In same jacket as # SR-27522. Double album.
          Catalog # B0002573-01; A-side Matrix # B0002573-01-C-RE1 RJ
        - Rootsman - Signs of the times; Funking radio stations, 1981; SR-27524; Rootsman (Box 64)
          No entry on Discogs.
          Catalog # BRS 1016; A-side Matrix # RM-002A KMW FWCJ
          B's Recording Inc.
        - Rootsman - Mister music man, 1988; SR-27525; Rootsman (Box 64)
          Catalog # LPL006; A-side Matrix # K LPL006-A RE
          Love People Records
        - Rose, Danny - Filthy dancing E.P., 1998; SR-27526; Rose, Danny (Box 64)
          Catalog # HAND 050T; A-side Matrix # DEDICATED TO RESEARCH @ INTERWAFFLE HAND-50-T-A
        - Rosetta Stone - Rosetta Stone, 1978; SR-27527; Rosetta Stone (Box 64)
          Catalog # PS 7011; A-side Matrix # C PS 7011-A KeeL-1
          Private Stock
        - Ross - Ross, 1974; SR-27528; Ross (Box 64)
          Catalog # SO 878; A-side Matrix # ST-S0-743079-A-1-11 AT
        - Ross, Diana - 20 Golden greats, 1981; SR-27529; Ross, Diana (Box 64)
          Catalog # 2-47.093; A-side Matrix # 2-47093A
          Spain
        - Ross, Diana - Greatest hits live (disc one), 1989; SR-27530; Ross, Diana (Box 64)
          In same jacket as # SR-27531. Double album.
          Catalog # EMDC 1001; A-side Matrix # EMDC 1001 A-1-1-1
        - Ross, Diana - Greatest hits live (disc two), 1989; SR-27531; Ross, Diana (Box 64)
          In same jacket as # SR-27530. Double album.
          Catalog # EMDC 1001; A-side Matrix # EMDC 1001 C-1-1-1
        - Ross, Diana - The boss, 1979; SR-27532; Ross, Diana (Box 64)
          Catalog # M8-923M1; A-side Matrix # M8-923R1A-18B
        - Ross, Diana - Why do fools fall in love, 1981; SR-27533; Ross, Diana (Box 64)
          In same jacket as # SR-27534. Different discs.
          Catalog # AFL1-4153-A; A-side Matrix # AFL1 4153 A
        - Ross, Diana - Mirror, mirror, 1981; SR-27534; Ross, Diana (Box 64)
          In same jacket as # SR-27533. Different discs.
          Catalog # JD-13022; A-side Matrix # PD 13022 A
        - Ross, Diana - Sing Motown, 1985; SR-27535; Ross, Diana; Supremes (Box 64)
          Catalog # 5371ML; A-side Matrix # 160 5371ML-A-15A ZDA #12
        - Ross, Jimmy - First true love affair, 1981; SR-27536; Ross, Jimmy (Box 64)
          Catalog # QRFC 002; A-side Matrix # QRFC-002-A-2
          Quality
          Scarborough, Ontario
        - Rough Trade - Avoid Freud, 1980; SR-27537; Rough Trade (Box 64)
          Catalog # USE 14; A-side Matrix # USE-14A-CP
        - Royal Flush - "Uh Oh"- suckers come to war; why? To die !, 1988; SR-27538; Royal Flush (Box 64)
          Catalog # RAP-101; A-side Matrix # UH-OH-A TLP
          Rap-A-Lot Records
          Houston, Texas
        - Royal House - Come over here, baby, 1990; SR-27539; Royal House (Box 64)
          In same jacket as # SR-27540. 2 copies.
          Catalog # WAR-2719; A-side Matrix # WAR-2719-A DMM DMS HERB IEJR SP1-1
          Warlock Records
        - Royal House - Come over here, baby, 1990; SR-27540; Royal House (Box 64)
          In same jacket as # SR-27539. 2 copies.
        - Royal House - Come over here, baby, 1990; SR-27541; Royal House (Box 64)
        - Royal House - Can you party, 1988; SR-27542; Royal House (Box 64)
          Catalog # WAR-2706; A-side Matrix # WAR-2706-A2 (RECUT2) 1-1 DCHARLES
          Idlers
        - Royal Kid - Jump to it remix, 1990; SR-27543; Royal Kid (Box 64)
          Catalog # M 533; A-side Matrix # R/S Alsdorf M 533-A
          !Hype
        - Royal Macadamians - Experiments in terror, 1990; SR-27544; Royal Macadamians (Box 64)
          In same jacket as # SR-27545. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 422-846 479-1; A-side Matrix # 422-846-479-1-AS-SP
        - Royal Macadamians - Experiments in terror, 1990; SR-27545; Royal Macadamians (Box 64)
          In same jacket as # SR-27544. 2 copies.
        - RPM - Phonogenic, 1984; SR-27546; RPM (Box 64)
          Catalog # 1-25079; A-side Matrix # B-19096-RA-SH1 1-25079-ARL1-SH1 SLM 6294 1-
        - Rubinel, Ronald - Tilda, 1987; SR-27547; Rubinel, Ronald (Box 64)
          Catalog # GD 41; A-side Matrix # MPO I GD 41 A10
        - Ruby - Rock & Roll madness, 1978; SR-27548; Ruby (Box 64)
          Catalog # PBR-7004; A-side Matrix # PBR-7004-A RE3 MBII
          PBR International
        - Rudder, David - Sketches, 1990; SR-27549; Rudder, David (Box 64)
          Catalog # CR 012; A-side Matrix # CR 012 -A- SKGTCMCS ROGER007
          Lypsoland
          Barbados
        - Rudder, David - Haiti, 1988; SR-27550; Rudder, David; Roots, Charlies (Box 64)
          Catalog # LONLP 60; A-side Matrix # LONLP 60 A-1U-1-1
        - Rudy - Just take my body, 1979; SR-27551; Rudy (Box 64)
          Catalog # PD-1-6226; A-side Matrix # A-2 PD-1-6226-AS-K
        - Rudy "Rude Dog" - Dog traxx vol.1, 1996; SR-27552; Rudy "Rude Dog" (Box 64)
          Catalog # JCL-0080; A-side Matrix # JCL 0080-A L-45932
          Groove Nation Records
        - Ruff Driverz - Don't stop, 1997; SR-27553; Ruff Driverz (Box 65)
          Catalog # TFERN 003; A-side Matrix # TFERN-003-A1
          Inferno
        - Ruffin, David - Ruffin & Kendrick, 1987; SR-27554; Ruffin, David; Kendrick, Eddie (Box 65)
          Catalog # 6765-1-R; A-side Matrix # A- 6765-1-R-A-2
        - Rufus & Chaka Khan - Street player, 1978; SR-24316; Rufus & Chaka Khan (Box 65)
          Catalog # AA-1049; A-side Matrix # S AA-1049-A 1F
          ABC Records
        - Rufus - Numbers, 1979; SR-27555; Rufus (Box 65)
          Catalog # AA-1098; A-side Matrix # AA-1098-A CS1 SX
        - Rufus - Party 'til you're broke, 1981; SR-27556; Rufus (Box 65)
          Catalog # MCA-5159; A-side Matrix # MCA-2443 KR-1
        - Ruiz, Frankie - … Voy pa' encima!, 1987; SR-27557; Ruiz, Frankie (Box 65)
          Catalog # 102-16073; A-side Matrix # D102-16073-D
          Top Hits
          Venezuela
        - Run DMC - Raising hell, 1986; SR-27558; Run DMC (Box 65)
          Catalog # PRO-1217; A-side Matrix # B PRO-1217-A
          Profile Records
        - Run DMC - Together forever - greatest hits 1983-1991 (disc one), 1991; SR-27559; Run DMC (Box 65)
          In same jacket as # SR-27560. Double album.
          Catalog # PRO-1419; A-side Matrix # PRO-1419-A 1-1
        - Run DMC - Together forever - greatest hits 1983-1991 (disc two), 1991; SR-27560; Run DMC (Box 65)
          In same jacket as # SR-27559. Double album.
          Catalog # PRO-1419; A-side Matrix # PRO-1419-C
        - Rush - Permanent waves, 1985; SR-27561; Rush (Box 65)